>>>This resume was generated entirely in Python. For full sourcecode, view my portfolio.

# **Omid Ghamiloo**

# Data Science & Analytics

I'm hard work and trying to improve my career through the given tasks. I may not know everything but I believe that you can google the solutions for all problems, but you need to know how to do it and my experiences can prove it. So, I try to do my best to learn and foster myself to grow in my position. I just need to love it. All the skills which are in this CV are my position. I also give credit to teamwork, so I try to be the best on that. You can find my data. analysis and web scraping projects on my github.

Email: omid.ghamiloo@gmail.com

Address: Rome, Italy Phone: +393891249525

Linkedin: /in/omid-ghamiloo/ Github: github.com/omidgh1 Website: ghamiloo.info

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Dirac s.r.l / Data Scientist

July 2021 - Present

Air pollution analysis and modelling
Air pollution mapping in high resolution scale by python and Arcgis
Web Scraping for marketing
Facebook digital marketing
Competitors analysis
AWS cloud

# Piersez / IT Administrator and Data Analyst

2016 - 2018

Microsoft Server installation and configuration Microsoft CRM Server base installation and configuration website develop Sale process analysis Sale analysis

## **Otolux / IT Administration**

2012 - 2015

Network developer and redesign the network layers website develop

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Master of Data Science - Sapienza University**

2018 - Present

Rome, Italy

Thesis: Air pollution mapping in high resolution scale

# **Bachelor of Information Technology - Eyvanakey University**

2010 - 2014

Tehran, Iran

Thesis: Cloud computing in applications

### Skills

#### Python

- Main Tools
  - > Pandas
  - > Numpy
- Data Mining
  - > Beautiful Soup
  - > Selenium
- Machine Learning
  - > Scikit-learn
  - > TensorFlow
- Data Visualization
  - > Mathplotlib
  - > Seaborn
- Web App
  - > Streamlit

## **IT Networking**

- Microsoft Server
  - > AD DS
  - > Group Policy
  - > Hyper v
  - > Storage Solution
- Vmware ESXi
- Veeam Backup
- Cisco Route and Switch
- Microsoft CRM
- Amazon AWS